[
    {
        "question_index": 1,
        "question_text": "Do you have a large car?",
        "correct_answer": "No, it's not very big.",
        "other_options": [
            "No, it's not very comfortable.",
            "No, it's not very colorful.",
            "No, it's not very fast."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 2,
        "question_text": "What do you find in the sports section of a newspaper?",
        "correct_answer": "football news",
        "other_options": [
            "political news",
            "funnies",
            "want ads"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 3,
        "question_text": "My chair is made of aluminum. What is it made of?",
        "correct_answer": "light metal",
        "other_options": [
            "strong plastic",
            "strong cloth",
            "light wood"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 4,
        "question_text": "This is a dangerous intersection. Why is it dangerous?",
        "correct_answer": "There are many people and heavy traffic.",
        "other_options": [
            "There is very little traffic.",
            "Only people use the streets.",
            "The sun always shines there."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 5,
        "question_text": "Birth is the beginning of life. What is the end of life?",
        "correct_answer": "death",
        "other_options": [
            "marriage",
            "illness",
            "shock"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 6,
        "question_text": "Maria wrote home twice last week.",
        "correct_answer": "She has written two letters.",
        "other_options": [
            "She sent only one letter last week.",
            "She sent four letters home last week.",
            "She will write home."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 7,
        "question_text": "Mary forgot the name of one of her friends.",
        "correct_answer": "She did not remember the name.",
        "other_options": [
            "She wrote down the name.",
            "She always remembered the name.",
            "She repeated the name aloud several times."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 8,
        "question_text": "Mrs. Jackson speaks English. Mrs. Smith does, too.",
        "correct_answer": "Both speak English.",
        "other_options": [
            "Mrs. Smith doesn't speak English.",
            "Mrs. Smith speaks two languages.",
            "Mrs. Jackson understands English but doesn't speak it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 9,
        "question_text": "The little girl had a problem when she tried to tie her shoes.",
        "correct_answer": "It was difficult for her to tie her shoes.",
        "other_options": [
            "It was easy for her to tie her shoes.",
            "She liked to tie her shoes.",
            "She disliked tying her shoes."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 10,
        "question_text": "Two of the teachers extinguished the fire.",
        "correct_answer": "They put out the fire.",
        "other_options": [
            "They started the fire.",
            "They looked for the fire.",
            "They reported the fire."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 11,
        "question_text": "Rose Ellen broke her mirror.\nShe couldn't ______.",
        "correct_answer": "see herself",
        "other_options": [
            "talk to anyone",
            "read her book",
            "tell time"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 12,
        "question_text": "I’m waiting for my brother to arrive. What am I waiting for?",
        "correct_answer": "my brother to get here",
        "other_options": [
            "my brother to drive",
            "my brother to start eating",
            "my brother to stop talking"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 13,
        "question_text": "The only painting I liked cost fifty dollars. Each of the other paintings was half that price.\nWhat was the price of the other paintings?",
        "correct_answer": "$25.00",
        "other_options": [
            "$50.00",
            "$75.00",
            "$100.00"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 14,
        "question_text": "Why are you so serious?",
        "correct_answer": "beacuse this is very important",
        "other_options": [
            "beacust the grass is green",
            "because I'm langhing",
            "because I'm smoking"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 15,
        "question_text": "How often do you practice English?",
        "correct_answer": "I practice English daily.",
        "other_options": [
            "I practice English at 4:00 o'clock.",
            "I practice English for two hours.",
            "Because I want to go to America."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 16,
        "question_text": "Can you tell me who that individual is?",
        "correct_answer": "He's the new instructor.",
        "other_options": [
            "He is going to town.",
            "He gave me one.",
            "He's at the library."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 17,
        "question_text": "Defense was their main concern. What was their main concern?",
        "correct_answer": "protection",
        "other_options": [
            "recreation",
            "information",
            "transformation"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 18,
        "question_text": "What is a board made of?",
        "correct_answer": "wood",
        "other_options": [
            "food",
            "wire",
            "leather"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 19,
        "question_text": "Why did you choose that book to read?",
        "correct_answer": "It was the only one I liked.",
        "other_options": [
            "I didn't want it.",
            "I couldn't find it.",
            "I got a good offer for it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 20,
        "question_text": "The woman kept her diamonds in a safe. Why?",
        "correct_answer": "so they would be secure",
        "other_options": [
            "so they would be worth more",
            "so they would shine",
            "so they would expand"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 21,
        "question_text": "I hear that your sister is living in England. Do you correspond with her?",
        "correct_answer": "Yes, I write a letter every week.",
        "other_options": [
            "Yes, I like to visit there.",
            "Yes, the people are friendly.",
            "Yes, the plane ticket is expensive."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 22,
        "question_text": "Jenny filled out the application. What did she do?",
        "correct_answer": "She completed it.",
        "other_options": [
            "She destroyed it.",
            "She lost it.",
            "She mailed it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 23,
        "question_text": "He’s catching on fast. What’s he doing?",
        "correct_answer": "He's learning quickly.",
        "other_options": [
            "He's making the paper longer.",
            "He's making the tape go faster.",
            "He's gluing the paper together."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 24,
        "question_text": "The commander says he approves of the plan.",
        "correct_answer": "He accepts the plan.",
        "other_options": [
            "He wants to move the plan.",
            "He doesn't agree with the plan.",
            "He wants to change it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 25,
        "question_text": "Make sure the equipment functions properly before you try to use it.",
        "correct_answer": "Make sure the equipment is working properly.",
        "other_options": [
            "Make sure the equipment is plugged in properly.",
            "Make sure the equipment is cleaned properly.",
            "Make sure the equipment is installed properly."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 26,
        "question_text": "When I called him, he was too occupied to talk.",
        "correct_answer": "He was busy.",
        "other_options": [
            "He was angry.",
            "He was sleepy.",
            "He was sick."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 27,
        "question_text": "Our guests stayed overnight.",
        "correct_answer": "They stayed all night.",
        "other_options": [
            "They never left their home.",
            "They stayed until midnight.",
            "They went home late."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 28,
        "question_text": "Joe was looking for a way to simplify his job.",
        "correct_answer": "He wanted to make his job easier.",
        "other_options": [
            "He wanted to abolish his job.",
            "He wanted to complicate his job.",
            "He wanted to make his job optional."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 29,
        "question_text": "Mr. Jones said, “I cannot afford a car.” What does Mr. Jones mean?",
        "correct_answer": "He doesn't have money to buy a car.",
        "other_options": [
            "He has enough money to buy a car.",
            "He needs a car.",
            "He doesn't need a car."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 30,
        "question_text": "Jane lives in Evanston, which is a suburb of Chicago. Where does Jane live?",
        "correct_answer": "close to Chicago",
        "other_options": [
            "close to Evanston",
            "in the center of Chicago",
            "in neither Evanston nor Chicago"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 31,
        "question_text": "Alfred removed the rest of the nails from the box. What did he remove?",
        "correct_answer": "the nails that were left",
        "other_options": [
            "only the large nails",
            "all the small nails",
            "half of the nails"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 32,
        "question_text": "The doctor has a new stethoscope. What does she have?",
        "correct_answer": "an instrument to listen to the heart",
        "other_options": [
            "a machine that takes pictures",
            "an instrument to measure temperature",
            "an instrument to check the stomach"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 33,
        "question_text": "We expect to arrive in town late at night.",
        "correct_answer": "We plan to arrive late.",
        "other_options": [
            "We don't like to arrive late.",
            "We never arrive late at night.",
            "We must arrive late at night."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 34,
        "question_text": "John asked, “How far is your hotel from here?” Tom said, “Not very far.”",
        "correct_answer": "Tom's hotel is close.",
        "other_options": [
            "Tom's hotel is a long way.",
            "Tom's hotel is quite far.",
            "Tom doesn't live in the hotel."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 35,
        "question_text": "I need a stamp.",
        "correct_answer": "I don't have any stamps.",
        "other_options": [
            "I bought a stamp.",
            "I am using a stamp.",
            "I have lots of stamps."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 36,
        "question_text": "I cashed my check at the bank.",
        "correct_answer": "I received some money for it.",
        "other_options": [
            "I was given a check at the bank.",
            "I lost my check at the bank.",
            "I left it at the cashier's."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 37,
        "question_text": "The airmen walked into the office with his hat on.",
        "correct_answer": "He entered without removing his hat.",
        "other_options": [
            "He left with his hat on.",
            "He forgot his hat at the office.",
            "He removed his hat when he entered."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 38,
        "question_text": "This office door is marked “private.”",
        "correct_answer": "There is a sign on the door.",
        "other_options": [
            "There is a window in the door.",
            "There is a line on the door.",
            "There is nail in the door."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 39,
        "question_text": "The man extended his hand.",
        "correct_answer": "He held it out.",
        "other_options": [
            "He removed it.",
            "He washed it.",
            "He cut it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 40,
        "question_text": "Joe said, “I’m really pressed for time.”",
        "correct_answer": "He has very little time.",
        "other_options": [
            "He has plenty of time.",
            "He is having a good time.",
            "He wants to know the time."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 41,
        "question_text": "He is willing to travel.",
        "correct_answer": "He is agreeing to travel.",
        "other_options": [
            "He is refusing to travel.",
            "He is forced to travel.",
            "He is afraid to travel."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 42,
        "question_text": "Jim encounters many people in his work.",
        "correct_answer": "He meets many people.",
        "other_options": [
            "He feeds many people.",
            "He instructs many people.",
            "He hires many people."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 43,
        "question_text": "Okay, you’ve convinced me.",
        "correct_answer": "You've persuaded me.",
        "other_options": [
            "You've made me dislike you.",
            "You've made me forget things.",
            "You've deceived me."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 44,
        "question_text": "The store put a number of things on sale. What did they do?",
        "correct_answer": "lowered the prices",
        "other_options": [
            "put them outside",
            "kept prices the same",
            "stopped selling"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 45,
        "question_text": "We turned off the water.",
        "correct_answer": "It stopped running.",
        "other_options": [
            "It started to run.",
            "We made it run faster.",
            "We forgot to stop it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 46,
        "question_text": "My father works for a lumber company. Where does he work?",
        "correct_answer": "in a forest",
        "other_options": [
            "in a library",
            "in a laboratory",
            "in a cemetery"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 47,
        "question_text": "Tools should be protected against moisture. What should they be protected against?",
        "correct_answer": "dampness",
        "other_options": [
            "dry weather",
            "oil and grease",
            "improper use"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 48,
        "question_text": "How will a new job enable him to buy a car?",
        "correct_answer": "He will earn enough money.",
        "other_options": [
            "He will need it to get to work.",
            "He will know how to drive then.",
            "He will have many new friends."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 49,
        "question_text": "Sam uses a tape measure in his work. What does he use?",
        "correct_answer": "a flexible measuring device",
        "other_options": [
            "a wooden measuring device",
            "a short measuring device",
            "an electrical measuring device"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 50,
        "question_text": "Arnold uses calipers in his workshop. What does he measure with them?",
        "correct_answer": "the thickness of metal",
        "other_options": [
            "the atmospheric pressure",
            "the water temperature",
            "the speed of sound"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 51,
        "question_text": "Ted said he would have a bit more. How much did he want?",
        "correct_answer": "a little more",
        "other_options": [
            "a lot more",
            "no more",
            "a few more"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 52,
        "question_text": "The soldier worked in transportation and supply. What did his job involve?",
        "correct_answer": "logistics",
        "other_options": [
            "personnel",
            "administration",
            "statistics"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 53,
        "question_text": "Sergeant Harris asked the mechanic, “When will you tear down the unit?” What did she\nwant to know?",
        "correct_answer": "when the unit will be disassembled",
        "other_options": [
            "when the unit will be in town",
            "when the unit will be sold",
            "when the unit will be assembled"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 54,
        "question_text": "The sailor can steer that small boat.",
        "correct_answer": "He can guide it.",
        "other_options": [
            "He can get in it.",
            "He can put water in it.",
            "He can take pictures of it."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 55,
        "question_text": "I’m running short of cash this week.",
        "correct_answer": "I'm getting low on money.",
        "other_options": [
            "I'm looking for a lost check.",
            "I'm running to the bank.",
            "I'm getting lots of money."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 56,
        "question_text": "You must tell the attorney nothing but the truth.",
        "correct_answer": "Tell him only the truth.",
        "other_options": [
            "Tell him part of the truth.",
            "Tell him nothing at all.",
            "Tell him all lies."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 57,
        "question_text": "M: What time is it?\nW: It’s eleven o’clock.\nM: I wish it were time to eat.\nWhat does the man mean?",
        "correct_answer": "He is hungry.",
        "other_options": [
            "He is tired.",
            "He is busy.",
            "He is late."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 58,
        "question_text": "M: Can you see anything?\nW: No, I need a flashlight.\nWhy can’t the woman see anything?",
        "correct_answer": "It is too dark.",
        "other_options": [
            "It is too bright.",
            "She is too short.",
            "She is blind."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 59,
        "question_text": "M: Do you want a glass of water?\nW: Yes, but I’d like some ice in it, please.\nWhy does the woman probably want ice?",
        "correct_answer": "She wants the water to be cold.",
        "other_options": [
            "She wants the water to be fresh.",
            "She wants the water to have bubbles in it.",
            "She wants the water to be clear."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 60,
        "question_text": "W: Where are we going on our vacation?\nM: I don’t know. It’s up to you.\nWhat did he tell her?",
        "correct_answer": "She must make the decision.",
        "other_options": [
            "She must go on a vacation.",
            "She must go by herself.",
            "She must stop bothering him."
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 61,
        "question_text": "M: Would you pass this information on to Mr. Brooks?\nW: Yes, I’ll be glad to.\nWhat will she do?",
        "correct_answer": "give Mr. Brooks the information",
        "other_options": [
            "evaluate the information for Mr. Brooks",
            "type the information for Mr. Brooks",
            "keep Mr. Brooks from getting the informatoin"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 62,
        "question_text": "W: When will you begin, Frank?\nM: As soon as the microphone is ready.\nWhat is Frank probably going to do?",
        "correct_answer": "give a talk",
        "other_options": [
            "take a picture",
            "look at the stars",
            "make a telephone call"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 63,
        "question_text": "W: Can you tell me what the compass says?\nM: No, I’m still trying to read it.\nWhat does the woman want to know?",
        "correct_answer": "the direction",
        "other_options": [
            "the temperature",
            "the distance",
            "the air speed"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 64,
        "question_text": "M: I’m looking for an article on preventive medicine.\nW: Here’s one in this magazine.\nWhat was the man doing?",
        "correct_answer": "searching for an article",
        "other_options": [
            "waiting for an article",
            "planning to write an article",
            "reading an article"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 65,
        "question_text": "Where are we going to camp?\nM: There’s a good place over by those big trees.\nWhat will they do?",
        "correct_answer": "sleep overnight",
        "other_options": [
            "rest for an hour",
            "take some pictures",
            "eat a big lunch"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 66,
        "question_text": "W: Attention, shoppers, we have a blue light special for you in our camera department. For\nthe next ten minutes only, you can receive a free photo album with the purchase of any digital\ncamera at regular price. That’s a blue light special in our camera department for the next ten\nminutes only.\nThe announcer said that ______ 10 minutes.",
        "correct_answer": "there's a special offer for",
        "other_options": [
            "digital cameras are on sale for",
            "the camera department closes in",
            "blue lights are on special for"
        ],
        "question_type": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 67,
        "question_text": "Texas has ______ roads than Nevada.",
        "correct_answer": "more",
        "other_options": [
            "the most",
            "the same",
            "like"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 68,
        "question_text": "______ day is today?",
        "correct_answer": "What",
        "other_options": [
            "Who",
            "That",
            "How"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 69,
        "question_text": "How do you know ______ ?",
        "correct_answer": "when I leave class",
        "other_options": [
            "when class leave I",
            "when leave class I",
            "I leave class when"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 70,
        "question_text": "Mr. Jones wants a car for ______.",
        "correct_answer": "transportation",
        "other_options": [
            "exercise",
            "eating",
            "sleeping"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 71,
        "question_text": "Do you have sufficient fuel in the tank?",
        "correct_answer": "enough",
        "other_options": [
            "synthetic",
            "solid",
            "some"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 72,
        "question_text": "Janice needed more data in order to finish the job.",
        "correct_answer": "facts",
        "other_options": [
            "time",
            "money",
            "machines"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 73,
        "question_text": "The judge told Joe to make an immediate decision.",
        "correct_answer": "Joe must decide quickly.",
        "other_options": [
            "Joe can give the answer tomorrow.",
            "The judge wants to decide about Joe.",
            "Joe wants to talk to the judge."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 74,
        "question_text": "We saw some _____ dishes on the floor.",
        "correct_answer": "broken",
        "other_options": [
            "breaking",
            "broke",
            "break"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 75,
        "question_text": "Tonight, _____ we go downtown with you?",
        "correct_answer": "may",
        "other_options": [
            "are",
            "have",
            "permit"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 76,
        "question_text": "The letter _____ yesterday.",
        "correct_answer": "was mailed",
        "other_options": [
            "mailed",
            "mails",
            "was mailing"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 77,
        "question_text": "I will be at the meeting if I _____ get away.",
        "correct_answer": "can",
        "other_options": [
            "ought to",
            "will",
            "might"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 78,
        "question_text": "Many of our libraries, especially in smaller cities, were made possible by Andrew Carnegie.\nBorn in Scotland, he came to the United States when he was thirteen. His money started many\nof the libraries in small cities of the United States.\nAccording to this paragraph, _____.",
        "correct_answer": "in smaller cities, many of the libraries were founded with Carnegie's funds",
        "other_options": [
            "libraries were not tax supported until Andrew Carnegie started them",
            "Andrew Carnegie was a native-born citizen of the United States",
            "libraries not founded by Carnegie were closed down"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 79,
        "question_text": "He cut the meat into pieces before serving it.",
        "correct_answer": "carved",
        "other_options": [
            "bought",
            "cooked",
            "cleaned"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 80,
        "question_text": "Bill refused to give up, so he tired to open the door _____.",
        "correct_answer": "again",
        "other_options": [
            "before",
            "also",
            "into"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 81,
        "question_text": "To learn something by yourself means to _____.",
        "correct_answer": "learn it without help",
        "other_options": [
            "study or practice with friends",
            "leave it alone",
            "learn by special classes"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 82,
        "question_text": "Jack had to insert a new sheet of paper.",
        "correct_answer": "put in",
        "other_options": [
            "buy",
            "remove",
            "exchange"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 83,
        "question_text": "I'd like to go to the air show next week, but I can't make it.",
        "correct_answer": "I want to go, but I'm going to be busy.",
        "other_options": [
            "I'm going to the air show.",
            "I don't care about the air show.",
            "The air show took place last week"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 84,
        "question_text": "George _____ do better work in school if he studied harder.",
        "correct_answer": "would",
        "other_options": [
            "will",
            "shall",
            "must"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 85,
        "question_text": "Did you hear that Janelle is _____ marry?",
        "correct_answer": "about to",
        "other_options": [
            "about",
            "about for",
            "about for to"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 86,
        "question_text": "The NCO expects his men _____ the proper uniform.",
        "correct_answer": "to wear",
        "other_options": [
            "wear",
            "be wearing",
            "are waering"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 87,
        "question_text": "After _____ the supplies, he locked up the storage room.",
        "correct_answer": "counting",
        "other_options": [
            "were counted",
            "count",
            "to count"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 88,
        "question_text": "They call him Bart.",
        "correct_answer": "He is called Bart.",
        "other_options": [
            "He has called Bart.",
            "He will call Bart.",
            "He is called Bart."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 89,
        "question_text": "Traffic on our streets is regulated by traffic lights.  By the same token, vitamins might be\ncalled the stop-and-go lights of the human body. Vitamins are necessary in order for the body\nto properly use the food it receives. The body needs only a small amount of vitamins, but they\nare important for protection against diseases. According to this paragraph, _____.",
        "correct_answer": "vitamins help prevent diseases",
        "other_options": [
            "there is a lot of traffic on the streets",
            "you must stop for a red light",
            "the body needs a large amount of vitamins"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 90,
        "question_text": "You may keep that shirt.",
        "correct_answer": "You don't have to return it.",
        "other_options": [
            "You have to wear it.",
            "You have to return it.",
            "You don't have to wear it."
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 91,
        "question_text": "It happened at 10 o'clock.",
        "correct_answer": "took place",
        "other_options": [
            "came",
            "went",
            "took charge"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 92,
        "question_text": "You should go on sick call right away.  You should _____.",
        "correct_answer": "go at once",
        "other_options": [
            "go to the right",
            "walk straight",
            "run away"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 93,
        "question_text": "When will you wind up the job?",
        "correct_answer": "finish",
        "other_options": [
            "start",
            "motivate",
            "join"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 94,
        "question_text": "Mr. Stein's piano recital was _____ one yet.",
        "correct_answer": "the most pallid",
        "other_options": [
            "most pallid",
            "more pallid",
            "more pallid than"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 95,
        "question_text": "Those immigrants _____ two months by the first of October.",
        "correct_answer": "will have been detained",
        "other_options": [
            "should be detained",
            "can detain",
            "will detain"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 96,
        "question_text": "People in cowboy clothes would probably look out _____ place at a symphony concert.",
        "correct_answer": "of",
        "other_options": [
            "on",
            "to",
            "by"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 97,
        "question_text": "When we heard the explosion, out first _____ was to hit the floor.",
        "correct_answer": "impulse",
        "other_options": [
            "noise",
            "thing",
            "jump"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 98,
        "question_text": "When you loosen this nut, it will _____.",
        "correct_answer": "come off",
        "other_options": [
            "be tightened",
            "crack",
            "stay tight"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    },
    {
        "question_index": 99,
        "question_text": "The evidence presented by the lawyer was not admiss_____.",
        "correct_answer": "-ible",
        "other_options": [
            "-ion",
            "-ibly",
            "-ive"
        ],
        "question_type": "reading"
    }
]